Meliodas stopped over in the town of Dalmary to treat his wounds.
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜ダルマリーの町で
傷を癒やしていたメリオダス＞
However, as part of the scheme of Golgius of the Weird Fangs,
＜ だが ｢不気味な牙｣
ゴルギウスの策略で➡
the town doctor, Dana,
made Meliodas drink poison.
町の医師 ダナによって
毒を飲まされてしまった＞
Due to a mysterious power,
he was able to recover from this setback.
＜謎の力で これをはね返し
窮地を脱するメリオダス＞
＜ しかし ｢不気味な牙｣は
更に 次の攻撃を仕掛けてくる＞
But the Weird Fangs have already begun setting up their next plan of attack.
Give back Captain!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長を返せ！
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)うっ！
Will they be able to defeat their enemy and rescue Ban, one of the Seven Deadly Sins,
＜彼らに打ち勝ち バステ監獄に
幽閉された七つの大罪➡
バンを救出することが
できるのであろうか＞
locked up at Baste Prison?
ドスッ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ぐはっ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)
へへっ そんなに名残惜しいのか？
Are you that sad to see me leaving?
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)この５年で
何一つ 学ばなかったようだな➡
Looks like you haven't learned a single thing in the past five years, Fox's Sin.
七つの大罪の強欲の罪｡➡
貴様に
どのような力があろうとも➡
Regardless of how strong you are,
you're powerless in the presence of Jude.
このジュドの前では無力｡
がはっ！
＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale of humans and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
＜国を守る聖騎士たちは
絶大なる魔力を有し➡
The Holy Knights who protected this country
wielded immensely powerful magic.
恐れ 敬われた＞
They were both feared and revered.
＜ だが その中で 国を裏切り➡
However,
a faction arose who betrayed their country and turned their blades against the remaining Knights.
全聖騎士を
敵に回した者たちがいた＞
To the masses, they were known as the "Seven Deadly Sins."
＜人々は
彼らを 七つの大罪と呼んだ＞
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
With unyielding emotions in tow,
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume o tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
Guided by my tenacity,
akiramenu omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume o tsunai da kimi to
Episode 6
The Verse of the Beginning
ドォーン！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)くっ… ああ～～！
ドスン ドスン ドスン ドスン！
You're pretty tough for a midget Holy Knight!
チビのくせに タフな聖騎士だな｡
You're pretty quick for a giant Holy Knight!
でかい割に
すばしっこい聖騎士だ｡
キン！
ドカッ！ ドカッ！
(ﾎｰｸ)
おわわ～…｡ あいつら 互いを➡
Do both of them think the other is a Holy Knight or something?
聖騎士だと思い込んでるのか？
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)そんな！
That's...
二人とも やめて｡ もうやめて！
Both of you, stop it!
Just stop it!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)あれ？
王女さん 何やってんの？
Huh? Princess? What are you doing?
そりゃ こっちのセリフだ！
あれ？ 団長も…｡
That's our line!
Huh, Captain's here too?
Where'd the Holy Knight go?
聖騎士は？
あっ そういえば…｡
Oh, speaking of which...
おっきいおねえちゃん
大丈夫？
Giant Lady! Are you okay?
あっ 君｡ まだ ここにいたの？
Ah, you're still here?
(子供)うん｡
チリーン
Yeah.
また みんな消えた｡
Everyone disappeared again.
チリーン
くっ！ 聖騎士め！
Damn Holy Knights.
Lord Meliodas, no!
メリオダス様 ダメ！ 僕 離れて｡
You, get away from there!
また みんなを隠したな!?➡
You hid everyone again, didn't you?!
ふん！
ドゴーン！
怖いよ！ 死にたくないよ～！
チリーン
Scary!
I don't wanna die!
ひぃ～！
大丈夫！
It's okay.
I'll protect you with my body if I have to.
私が
この身に代えても守ってみせます｡
(父)あ… あんたが？
はい！
You?
Yes!
What a caring princess.
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)なんて 民思いの王女様｡
あっ｡
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)でも
その言葉 どこまで本物かしら～？
I wonder how true those words of yours are, though.
まさか こいつ 聖騎士!?
Don't tell me... She's a Holy Knight?
ぎゃあ～～！
Storm Rondo!
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)嵐の輪舞｡
さあ きゃわいい私のクソ虫ども➡
Come, my cute little bugs!
鋭い角と羽で
肉を切り裂くのよ！
Tear their flesh apart with your hard claws and sharp wings!
Storm Rondo
Wah! I'm scared! I'm so scared!
いや 怖い！ 怖いよ～！
Such an annoying brat.
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)
ぎゃあぎゃあ うるせぇガキ！➡
まずは あんたからだよ｡ 死ね！
I'll start with you!
Die!
Hmm,
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)
え～っと この身に代えても➡
"I'll protect you with my body if I have to," was it?
守ってみせます…
だったかしら？➡
You know how to sound cool,
口では かっこいいこと言っても➡
心の中じゃ 誰かの助けを
期待しているんでしょう？
but deep down, you're hoping someone else will come to the rescue, aren't you?
So cruel!
ひっでぇ｡
ん？ エリザベスちゃん!?
Elizabeth?
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)マ… マジ？
R-Really?
私 約束しましたよね｡
I... made a promise, right?
たとえ あなたが死んでも…｡
Even if you were to die...
私が
一人ぼっちになったとしても➡
Even if I'm the only one left...
I will protect the kingdom and its people from the Holy Knights.
王国と人々を
聖騎士たちから守るって｡
(子供)おねえちゃん！
Lady!
エリザベスちゃん…｡
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ちっ！
Elizabeth?
うわっ！ 大丈夫か!?
Are you okay?
Yes.
ええ…｡
あなた どこもケガはない？
Are you hurt anywhere?
チリーン
ふむ｡ こんな子供すら➡
No.
It's quite admirable that you would even put your body in harm's way to protect a child.
身を挺して守るとは
殊勝な心掛けよ｡
チリーン
(子供)だが…｡
But...
Reality is harsh.
(ﾙｲﾝ)現実は残酷じゃ｡
子供が聖騎士に｡ 今までのは幻？
The kid turned into a Holy Knight?
So his appearance until now was an illusion?!
まさか 二人がおかしくなったのも
あなたが？
So then, you're also the reason those two are acting strange?
(ﾙｲﾝ)ファッファッファッ！
七つの大罪も➡
Before me, the Seven Deadly Sins are like mere children.
わしの前では 小童も同然よ｡
Turn them back to normal!
二人を元に戻して！
くっ… ううっ！
(ﾙｲﾝ)ふん！
ああっ…｡
やろう～‼
You bastard!
(ﾙｲﾝ)ふん！
ぎゃあ～！ うっ…｡
(ﾙｲﾝ)ファッファッ…➡
今頃 七つの大罪も
互いに殺し合って➡
Those two Sins are probably killing each other by now.
命も尽きるころじゃ｡
Their lives are about to reach their ends.
二人を元に… 戻しなさい！
Return those two... back to normal!
(ﾙｲﾝ)んん～！
ガン！
Elibabeph!
エリザベプびゃ～ん‼
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)
ちょっと ルイン｡ 王女様は➡
Wait, Ruin. Wouldn't it be bad if we killed the princess?
殺しちゃまずいんじゃな～い？
(ﾙｲﾝ)
ふん そのくらい心得ておるわ｡➡
I'm fully aware of that.
王女エリザベスよ➡
Hey, Princess Elizabeth.
I'll tell you something in
commendation of your bravery.
その勇気に免じて
一つ教えてやろう｡➡
ヤツらにかけた
催眠暗示の正体じゃ｡➡
The thing that hypnotized those two is...
the bell of this staff—
それは この錫杖の… あっ ない！
It's gone?!
Y-You wench!
(ﾙｲﾝ)こ… この小娘 まさか
はなから それを狙って…｡➡
You were going after the bell all along!
よくも…
よくも やってくれたな～！➡
How dare you?
How dare you do this?
ふん！ ファッ？
そっちこそ
よくも やってくれたな｡
No.
How dare you?
(ﾙｲﾝ)
くっ… ぬっ？ 術が解けたか｡➡
The spell was broken?
エリザベス｡
Elizabeth...
お前の覚悟 しっかり受け止めたぜ｡
I'm convinced of your dedication.
(ﾙｲﾝ)無視か！ 先手必勝～！
Ignoring me?!
He who strikes first, wins!
ガン！
(ﾙｲﾝ)ぬあぁ～～！
メリオダス！
Meliodas!
(ﾙｲﾝ)ファッファッ… くだらん｡➡
What a joke.
王国も こんな小童に
神経質になりおって｡
To think that the kingdom is
terrified of such a small child.
(ﾙｲﾝ)うわぁ～～！
うひゃ～！
(ﾙｲﾝ)うわぁ～～…｡
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)あっ ちょっと ルイン！
Hey, wait, Ruin!
ボキッ(指を鳴らす音)
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)はっ！
(ﾙｲﾝ)ぐわぁ～！
ドーン！
(衛兵たち)うわっ！
What the?
なんだ!?
人が 吹っ飛んできたぞ！
A person just came flying over?!
(ﾙｲﾝ)げほっ げほっ…｡ ん？
ゴン！
(ﾙｲﾝ)うわっ！
(ﾙｲﾝ)ファ… ファ… ファ…➡
Yes... It'd be boring if it weren't like this.
そうだ｡
そうでなくてはつまらん｡➡
Right, Dragon's Sin, Meliodas?!
なあ？ 憤怒の罪のメリオダス｡
ま… まさか
七つの大罪の団長の…｡
Don't tell me he's the Captain of the Seven?!
ドゴン！
(２人)ひぃ…｡
(ﾙｲﾝ)まさか 拳一つで➡
To break my armor with a single punch...
わしの鎧を打ち砕くとは➡
I-Impressive.
み… 見事…➡
Is that what you were
expecting me to say? You fool!
とでも言うと思うか バカめ！➡
ぬおぉ～！ こんな鎧などは➡
This armor is nothing more than shallow skin!
薄皮の一枚にすぎん｡➡
わしの真の鎧は
鋼に勝る この肉体！➡
My true armor is this body,
which is stronger than steel!
So! What will you do—
さあ どうす…｡
ドゴン！
(ﾙｲﾝ)ぐわっ…｡
I don't have a choice.
しょうがねぇ｡ お前は
俺の大切なもんを傷つけた｡
You hurt someone important to me.
(ﾙｲﾝ)ううっ！ あぁ…｡ ごふっ…｡
それが お前の罪だぜ｡
That is your sin!
聖騎士様を一撃で…｡
Lord Ruin...
In one hit...
ほ… 本物だ｡
本物の七つの大罪だ！
He's the real deal...
He's really one of the Seven Deadly Sins!
(衛兵)逃げろ～！
Run for it!
Five years ago...
(ﾊﾞﾝ)５年前 俺が なんで➡
Do you know why I was
captured by you five years ago?
てめぇに捕まったか 分かるか？
あんときの俺は
痛みが欲しかったんだ｡
Back then, I longed to feel pain...
生きてるって実感を感じられる
苦痛が欲しかったんだよ｡➡
Pain that could make me feel truly alive....
But I'm sick of your pain already.
でも もう飽きたわ お前の痛みは｡
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)あっ…｡
団ちょが生きてるとなりゃ➡
Since now I know that Cap'n is alive,
things are bound to get interesting, right?
また
いろいろ 事が起こりそうだろ？
There's no reason for me to stick
around in this boring place anymore!
こんな つまらん所で
くすぶってる理由も➡
なくなったわけだ｡
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)あぁ…｡ き… 貴様➡
B-Bastard!
You're not planning the same thing as ten
years ago, are you? Overthrowing the kingdom?
まさか
１０年前のように王国の転覆を…｡
王国転覆？
Overthrowing the kingdom?
あったな そんなこと｡
Oh yeah, now that you mention it.
Just try something like that.
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)
そんなことしてみろ｡ 今度こそ➡
This time, for sure,
王国全騎士は
貴様ら七つの大罪に➡
every single Holy Knight in the kingdom will declare all-out war on the Seven Deadly Sins—
全面戦争を仕掛けるぞ… ぐおっ！
へっ｡ そそるねぇ｡
Sounds like fun.
あぁ… ごめんな
エリザベスちゃん｡
I'm sorry, Elizabeth.
If only I were stronger.
俺に もっと力があればよぉ…｡
Those are some serious injuries.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)すごいケガだね｡
すぐ 町まで連れていかなきゃ｡
We need to get her back to town right away.
Please... wait...
待って… ください…｡
Please... take me with you...
私も 連れていってください…➡
Where Lord Meliodas... and Lord Ban are...
メリオダス様とバン様のもとに｡
What are you saying? You're severely wounded!
何言ってんだよ そんな傷で！
I made... a promise.
私は 約束したんです…｡
I will continue fighting... for the sake of protecting the kingdom and its people.
王国と人々を守るために➡
戦い続けると｡
I'm sorry, but that's impossible.
残念だけど 無理だよ｡
ディアンヌ様…｡
Lady Diane?
We're going to Baste Prison,
where the enemy is awaiting us, you know.
これから向かうのは
敵が待ち構えてるバステ監獄だよ｡
そんな体で行っても
何もできない｡
Even if you go, you can't do
anything in your current condition.
そうですよね｡ 確かに➡
That's true.
You're right that I don't have any power.
私には 力がありません｡
I can't argue... or fight against a Holy Knight...
聖騎士と渡り合うことも➡
戦うこともできません｡
でも…｡
あっ｡
But...
Even then...
それでも メリオダス様と…➡
with Lord Meliodas...
And everyone else... We decided to go together.
皆さんと共に
歩んでいこうと決めたんです｡
約束を果たすために｡
In order to fulfill the promise.
So you won't cry, huh?
泣かないんだね｡
はい｡
No.
僕のリュックの中に入れてあげる｡
でも 揺れるよ｡
I'll put you inside of my bag.
It'll be a bumpy ride.
もしかしたら
傷に障るかもしれない｡
Your wounds might get worse as well.
それでもいい？
ディアンヌ様…｡
Is that still okay?
Lady Diane!
はい！
ん？
Yes!
Huh?
おい！
ひっ！
Hey!
てめぇ バステの兵士だな!?
You're a soldier from Baste, aren't you?
あっ いや…
俺はただ 聖騎士様に脅されて…｡
N-No, I was threatened by a Holy Knight—
監獄に捕まっている七つの大罪と➡
You know the location of the captured Sin and the doctor's daughter, don't you?
医者の娘の居場所を知ってるな!?
待ってくれ！
そんなこと話したら➡
Wait!
Do you have any idea what the Holy Knights will do to me if I tell you—
聖騎士様に
どんな目に遭わされるか… ひっ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)聖騎士と… 僕らに
こんな目に遭わされるのと➡
Between the Holy Knights
and us, who'd you prefer?
どっちがマシ？
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)きぅ～…｡
ほんとに この塔なのか？
Are you sure it's this tower?
I'm sure of it.
間違いないよ｡ 僕を前にして➡
He didn't seem like the type of
soldier who'd lie to my face about this.
うそをつけるような兵士には
見えなかったもん｡
そっか｡ ありがとな エリザベス｡
I see.
Thanks, Elizabeth.
But it sure is awfully empty in here.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)しっかし
ものの見事に もぬけの殻だね｡
It's probably because I sent their boss flying.
聖騎士 吹っ飛ばしたのが
よっぽど こたえたんだろ｡
しょぼい連中だぜ｡
What a cowardly bunch.
Looks like they've gone inside.
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)中に入ったようです｡➡
いかがしますか？ ゴルギウス様｡
What are your orders, Lord Golgius?
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
さすがと言っておきましょう｡➡
I must admit that I'm impressed.
だが
その強さは あなたたち自身が➡
However, your strength will bring
your own agonizing death upon you!
苦しみ悶える死を招いてしまった｡
はっ｡ それは 呪言の玉｡
That's the incantation ball?
ボゥン！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)うっ！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)これは…｡
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)永劫封印術｡➡
This...
The Eternal Seal Spell!
「暴龍」１０体をもってしても➡
Even ten tyrant dragons would be unable to destroy this magical containment barrier.
Eternal Seal Spell
破壊不能の強力な隔離魔法障壁｡➡
イヒヒヒ… 七つの大罪は➡
All the Sins can do is rot away
in agony inside that sealed cage!
この閉ざされた檻の中で
朽ち果てるのみ｡
この子だ｡
医者の娘｡ 間違いない｡
That's her.
There's no doubt about it.
She's the doctor's daughter.
連れていくぞ｡
リュックに もう一人 入るか？
Let's take her with us.
Can you fit another person inside your bag?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)うん 大丈夫｡
Yup, should be fine!
(ｾﾈｯﾄ)きゃあ～！
バキン！
大丈夫か？
Is she okay?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)うん 気絶してるだけ｡
≫タッ タッ…(足音)
Yup, looks like she just fainted.
バン｡
あっ 団ちょ｡
Ban.
Ah, Cap'n!
They just reunited, so what's with the tension in the air?
再会早々 何？ この雰囲気｡
な～んか やばい予感が…｡
正解｡
I have a bad feeling about this...
Yep.
僕の後ろに隠れた方がいいよ｡
えっ!?
You should hide behind me.
バ～ン！
団ちょ～！
Ban!
Cap'n!
あははっ！
(２人)ほっ ほっ ほっ ほっ…｡
Phew, they get along really well!
なんだ むちゃくちゃ
仲いいじゃんかよ｡
うん｡
団ちょ！
Yeah...
Cap'n!
あははっ！ 団ちょも ほら～！
よっ！
Come on, Cap'n!
What in the world?
どゆこと？
ほっといていいよ｡
Just let them be.
なんだよ
すっかり なまってると思ったら…｡
The hell?
I thought you'd be sluggish by now, but...
元気そうだな｡
You seem pretty energetic!
レディー…｡
ゴー！
Ready?
Go!
な… なんだ!?
Wh-What's going on?!
昔から
あの二人って こんな感じなんだ｡
Those two have always been like this.
どんな感じだよ！
ほんと 男って子供だよね｡
What do you mean, like this?
Really, men are so childish...
Our record was 361 wins
out of 720 in my favor, right?
団ちょとの戦績は ７２０戦中➡
俺の３６１勝だよな｡
お前 寝ぼけてんな｡
俺が３６１勝だ！
Are you sleep-talking?
I'm the one with 361 wins!
んん～！
うおぉ～！
ふふっ！
団長 むきになった顔もかわいい｡
Captain's serious face is so cute, too!
Now's not the time for that!
うわぁ～！
ドドーーン！
The barrier!
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)結界が…｡
バカな！
Impossible!
This is how powerful the Seven Deadly Sins are?
これが
七つの大罪の力だというのか｡
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)一旦… 撤退します｡
I'm retreating... temporarily.
えっ？ ちょっ… ちょっと！
Wait... wait!
(ｾﾈｯﾄ)お父さん お父さん！➡
Dad? Dad?!
ああ… お父さん！
Dad!
(ﾀﾞﾅ)おお～ セネット！
無事でよかった｡
Cenette! I'm so glad you're safe!
Same to you, Father...
(ｾﾈｯﾄ)
お父さんこそ｡ 私 てっきり…｡
I thought you'd be...
うわっ！
い… 生き返った!?
H-He came back to life?!
(ﾀﾞﾅ)見てくれ｡
Take a look.
This is...
これは
メリオダスの傷のときと同じだぜ｡
It's the same thing that
happened with Meliodas's wound!
(ﾀﾞﾅ)同じ？
恥ずかしながら 医者の私にも➡
The same thing?
It's embarrassing to say this as a doctor, but... I have no idea how I survived.
なぜ生きてるのか
さっぱり分からないんだ｡
Well, you're alive.
こうして生きてるんだから
それでいいんじゃねぇのか｡
That's what matters, right?
じゃあ 俺たちは行くぜ｡
話を聞きつけた聖騎士が➡
Anyway, we're off.
Once the Holy Knights hear about this, there's a chance they'll march straight into this town.
この町に乗り込んでこないとも
かぎらないからな｡
(ﾀﾞﾅ)メリオダス君！
ん？
Meliodas!
Is there any way for me to return the favor?
何か礼をさせてくれないか｡➡
せめて ささやかな食事でも｡
Even if it's as simple as a meal.
Well, I guess I'll take you up on that offer.
それじゃ お言葉に甘えるかな｡
Please, no poison this time.
毒入りは勘弁な｡
プゴッ｡
エリザベスの具合は？
How's Elizabeth?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)だいぶ 落ち着いたみたい｡
She's calmed down a lot.
I see.
そっか｡
なんで メリオダスの部屋で➡
Why exactly is she sleeping in your room?
寝てるんだ？
エリザベスちゃんの部屋は➡
Elizabeth's room is on the third floor, y'know.
３階だろ｡
それがさぁ➡
About that...
バンのヤツ エリザベスのベッド
勝手に取っちゃって➡
Ban just went ahead and slept on Elizabeth's bed,
claiming that it's his room now.
ここ 自分の部屋にするって｡
あっ じゃあ エリザベスちゃんは
どうすんだよ？
Then what's Elizabeth going to do?
俺と一緒でいいんじゃねぇか｡
そうだな｡
She'll be fine sleeping with me.
That works.
ほかに部屋もないし
しかたなく… ねぇ～よ！
There are no other rooms so there's nothing we can do—
As if!
んん… セネットさん…｡
Cenette?
あっ バン様は？
Where's Lord Ban?
We brought both of them
back to town, safe and sound.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)二人とも 無事見つかって
町に戻ってきたよ｡➡
そのほかのみんなも無事｡
そう… よかった｡
Everyone else is safe too.
I see. I'm glad.
I'm so glad...
よかった…｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)今度は泣くんだね｡
ふふっ｡
So this time you are crying, huh?
That's true.
そうですね｡
Well then, Elizabeth. I'll introduce him again.
さてと エリザベス｡
改めて紹介する｡
This is the Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban.
強欲の罪 強欲の罪のバンだ｡
まっ よろしく頼むわ｡
Yo, nice to meet ya.
Where did those clothes come from?
お前 その服は？
(ﾊﾞﾝ)王女の前で➡
There's no way I could be
naked in front of the princess.
裸でいるわけにはいかねぇだろ｡
服買う金なんて持ってたのかよ｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)落ちてたんだよ｡➡
You had money on you to buy clothes?
I just happened to find them lying around.
たまたま｡ 偶然｡
(回想)
((おい見ろ｡ あいつ 裸だぜ))
Hey, look. That guy's walking around naked.
はぁ…｡
(ﾊﾞﾝ)そういやぁ➡
Come to think of it, it's been a while, Diane.
ディアンヌも久しぶりだな｡
僕は もう１００年➡
I could've gone without seeing you
for another hundred years, though.
君と会わなくても
よかったんだけど｡
エリザベスです｡
こんな格好で申し訳ありません｡
I'm Elizabeth.
Please forgive me for greeting you in such a state.
No need, Princess.
いえいえ 王女様｡
うちらは無礼講です｡
We Sins aren't really ones for decorum.
四人で 仲よくしようぜ｡
Here's to the four of us getting along.
五人だろ 五人｡
Five. There are five of us.
あっ？ ぼけんなよ 団ちょ｡
四人だろ？
Huh? Don't be silly, Cap'n.
Of course it's the four of us.
五人だろ？ 頭のねじ
緩み過ぎてんじゃねぇのか？
It's five!
Do you have a screw loose
in your head or something?
ああ？ 誰だ？
Huh? Who's there?
俺だ｡
Me!
豚がしゃべってる！
The pig can talk?!
Why's that freaking you out now?!
今更 そこでビビるか～!?
うそだろ!?
No way! What's the point of a pig being able to talk like a person?
人の言葉しゃべる豚なんて
全く無意味だろ！
分かった！ お前 キングだろ｡➡
Oh, I get it. You, you're King, right?
I see you were cursed and turned into a pig, huh?
そっかぁ｡ 呪いをかけられて
ついに 豚になっちまったか｡
You're wrong.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)違うよ｡
キングは死んだ｡ 噂だけどな｡
King died.
So the rumors say.
ふ～ん｡
言っとくが➡
I'll have you know, I'm not just some ordinary pig.
俺は ただの豚じゃねぇ｡
残飯処理騎士団 団長ホーク様だ！
I'm Hawk, the captain of the
Knights of Leftovers Disposal!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)すげぇ！ 全然聞いたことねぇ！
えっへん！
Amazing!
I've never heard of anything like this before!
挨拶は済んだかね？
Finished with the introductions yet?
さあ 冷めないうちに
どんどん食べてくれ｡
Eat up before the food gets cold.
さっ 食べようぜ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)あっ 団ちょ ずりぃ～！
Well, let's eat!
Cap'n, no fair!
残飯は この
残飯処理騎士団のものだからな！
Leftovers belong to the Knights of Leftovers Disposal, okay!
(ｾﾈｯﾄ)はい お二人もどうぞ｡➡
Here, this is for you two.
I'm sorry that you're the
only one eating standing up.
一人だけ立食で すみません｡
ううん｡ 僕は みんなと一緒に➡
No, that's okay.
I'm glad that I get to eat with everyone!
ご飯できるだけで楽しいから｡
Don't be so harsh, Cap'n Hawk!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)堅いこと言うなよ
ホーク団ちょ～｡➡
お願いします 師匠～｡
こいつ なんとかしてくれぇ…｡
Please, Master...
Someone, do something about him...
Ban, stop being such a pain!
バン むちゃしちゃダメだよ｡
ふふっ｡
I wish this moment could last forever.
こんな時間が
もっと続けばいいのに｡
But that's impossible, isn't it?
でも そういうわけには
いかないんですよね｡
Hey, Princess...
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ねえ 王女さん｡
あっ｡
I don't know anything about humans or their countries.
僕は 人間や
人間の国の事情は知らないし➡
Honestly, I'm not really interested, either...
正直 興味もない｡ でも…｡
でも？
But...
But?
I don't think I'd mind fighting for you.
君のためなら
戦ってもいいと思った｡
今日の君が
あんまり かっこよかったから｡
You were really cool today.
That's...
そんな！ わ… 私は何も…｡
I-I didn't do any—
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
君には ちゃんと 力があるよ｡➡
You definitely have a power within you.
The power to move the hearts of Captain and me...
僕や団長の心を動かす力が｡
ディアンヌ様…｡
Lady Diane...
By the way, Princess...
ねえ 王女さん｡
はい？
Yes?
エリザベスって呼んでもいい？
Can I call you... Elizabeth?
はい！
Yes!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)じゃあさ 僕のことも
｢様｣付けしなくていいからね｡
You don't have to address me with "Lady," either.
えっ？ それは…｡
But that's—
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)いいから！
は… はい｡
It's fine!
Okay!
Father, the sky...
父さん 空を…｡
あっ！➡
これは…｡ まるで
ブリタニアの古い詩の一節の…｡
This is...
Just like that stanza from one of the ancient poems of Britannia...
(ﾀﾞﾅ)
｢一天を流星が十字に斬り裂く時➡
When the skies are crisscrossed with shooting stars,
Britannia will be visited by a dreadful menace.
ブリタニアを
至大の脅威が見舞う｡➡
It is the omen of the beginning of a trial of ancient origins.
それは
古より定められし試練にして➡
Between those guided by the hand of light,
光の導き手と 黒き血脈の➡
and those of the bloodline of darkness,
a holy war shall begin.
聖戦の始まりの兆しとならん｣｡
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
ittari kitari de ikidomari yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and defy them all to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang HAJI ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
Let's go, now we can fly high
iku ze Now we can fly high
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)メリオダスとデｨアンヌに
バンが合流した｡
Ban has joined up with Meliodas and Diane.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
ふ～ん｡ なんで今頃になって➡
I don't know why they
decided to make a move now.
動きだそうとしてるんだか｡
Don't you dare betray my trust...
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)
私の信頼を裏切らないでくれよ➡
キング｡
King.
Next Episode's Report
Finally, the Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban, joins the crew!
＜ ようやく 旅の仲間に
強欲の罪のバンが加わった＞
(ﾊﾞﾝ)よろしくお願いしやっす｡
団ちょ 酒！
Nice to meet you all!
Cap'n, let's drink!
＜ いつも飲んでいるが
すこぶる 酒には弱い＞
He always drinks, but he can't hold his liquor!
＜ そして
実は すごく料理がうまい＞
Also, he's really good at cooking!
そいつは楽しみだぜ！
I'm looking forward to that!
＜ だが ﾎｰｸは気付いていなかった｡
料理が うまいということは➡
However, Hawk didn't realize that being good at cooking means there'll be less leftovers.
それだけ 残飯の量が
減るのだということに＞
次回 『七つの大罪』 ｢感動の再会｣｡
Next time, on The Seven Deadly Sins: "The Touching Reunion."
安心しろ ホーク｡
お前の残飯だけは俺が作ってやる｡
No need to worry, Hawk.
I'll make sure you have plenty of leftovers.
Episode 7
The Touching Reunion
I'll make sure you have plenty of leftovers.
できれば 遠慮したい｡
Please spare me, if you can.
今日は国山アナウンサーが
スポーツコーナーを担当します｡
安倍総理は第２次政権発足から